Dennis Roberts fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Audio recordings, 1968 - 1982; F-160-2; 132 sound recordings; Physical description: series includes 134 audio cassettes and 4 audio tapes (reel-to-reel).
  - Jack Webster interviews: Dr. Clark (Academic Planning, UBC), David Anderson and Allan Williams, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-40 (Audio cassette OBJ-3392)
    B - Webster with David Anderson and Allan Williams (Government's version of Egg Marketing) (Also raises the question as to whether Pierre Trudeau was fibbing when he claimed he actually said "Fuddle-Duddle" in the House.)
    Robert M. Clark; Webster, Jack; Anderson, David; Williams, Allan; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-118.1 orig., F-160-item118.
  - Art Finley (CKNW) interviews re ecology, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-41 (Audio cassette OBJ-3393)
    A, B - Art Finlay (CKNW) with interviews re the ecology ranging from population explosion to pollution
    CKNW Radio; Finley, Art; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-119.1 orig., F-160-item119.
  - Prof. George Keter (History); Robert Brown (Dean), [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-42 (Audio cassette OBJ-3394)
    A - Prof. George Keter, History Dept. interview.
    B - Robert Brown, Dean, IDS, on new General Studies Program with retiring Peak reporter (sounds like John Sawatsky)
    George Keter; Brown, Robert C.; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-120.1 orig., F-160-item120.
  - Prof. Bill Vidaver; Prof. Weinberg, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-43 (Audio cassette OBJ-3395)
    A - Prof. Bill Vidaver re Environmental Studies program.
    B - Prof. Weinberg re IQ - EEG.
    Vidaver, Bill; Weinberg, Hal; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-121.1 orig., F-160-item121.
  - Dr. Norman MacKenzie, Open University in Britain; "Enfilmony", [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-44 (Audio cassette OBJ-3396)
    A - Dr. Norman MacKenzie, Open University in Britain.
    B - "Enfilmony" (environment, film and the symphony performance planned to take place on the Mall and conducted by Brent Straughan, Student, who created it).
    Norman MacKenzie; Straughan, Brent; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-122.1 orig., F-160-item122.
  - Jack Webster / Dr. Norman MacKenzie, Open University; Russian poet interview., 21 March 1973; F-160-2-0-0-0-67 (Audio cassette OBJ-3417)
    A, B - Jack Webster / Dr. Norman MacKenzie, Open University cont'd // Russian poet interview.
    Webster, Jack; Norman MacKenzie; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-123.1 orig., F-160-item123.
  - Student recruitment; Jack Webster / Dave Barrett interview, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-45 (Audio cassette OBJ-3397)
    A - Student recruitment discussion // music.
    B - Jack Webster / Dave Barrett, B.C. Premier.
    Webster, Jack; Barrett, Dave; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-124.1 orig., F-160-item124.
  - Profs. Bill Ross and Ray Duncan; Houghton, [ca 1969]; F-160-2-0-0-0-19 (Audio cassette OBJ-3372)
    A - Physical Development Studies Program with Profs. Bill Ross and Ray Duncan. B - Houghton / Behavioural Sciences Foundation // Pollution
    Ross, William; Duncan, Ray; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-125.1 orig., F-160-item125.
  - SFU Alumni Association Board meeting, 17 November 1982; F-160-2-0-0-0-132 (Audio cassette OBJ-3488)
    A, B - SFU Alumni Association Board Meeting.
    Simon Fraser University Alumni Association; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-126.1 orig., F-160-item126.
  - First SFU Open House; Jack Webster / Harry Evans (SFU) and Jack Parnell (UBC), 1975; F-160-2-0-0-0-90 (Audio cassette OBJ-3442)
    A, B. - SFU First Open House - Jack Webster discusses admissions with Registrars Harry Evans, SFU and Jack Parnell, UBC
    Webster, Jack; Evans, Harry M.; Jack Parnell; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-127.1 orig., F-160-item127.
  - Profs. Glen Geen and Louis Druehl; Prof. Bill Vidaver, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-46 (Audio cassette OBJ-3398)
    A - Marine Biology Station with Profs. Glen Geen and Louis Druehl.
    B - Prof. Bill Vidaver discusses pollution
    Geen, Glen H.; Druehl, Louis; Vidaver, Bill; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-128.1 orig., F-160-item128.
  - Lakie Sirimanne, Economics and Commerce student, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-47 (Audio cassette OBJ-3399)
    A, B - Lakie Sirimanne, Economics and Commerce student from Ceylon; came to Canada to join RCAF
    Lakie Sirimanne; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-129.1 orig., F-160-item129.
  - "Post-Occupation" News Conference, letters between President Stand and Student Council and Attorney General, 1968; F-160-2-0-0-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-3360)
    A, B - "Post-Occupation" News Conference // Letters between President Stand and Student Council and Attorney General read over phone by DR to news outlets
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-130.1 orig., F-160-item130.
  - Dr. Strand addressing department Chairs after Palmer decision, [ca 1970]; F-160-2-0-0-0-50 (Audio reel OBJ-1062)
    Dr. Strand addressing department Chairs after Palmer decision
    Pending review
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: R-160-2-0-131.1 orig., F-160-item131.
  - Dr. Strand press conference, 24 November 1968; F-160-2-0-0-0-11 (Audio reel OBJ-1063)
    Dr. Strand press conference
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: R-160-2-0-134.1 orig., F-160-item134.
  - Dr. Strand, 30 September [1969?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-24 (Audio reel OBJ-1064)
    Dr. Strand
    Strand, Kenneth; Strand, Kenneth; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: R-160-2-0-132.1 orig., F-160-item132.
  - Professor Rieckhoff interviewed by Dennis Roberts, 7 January 1972; F-160-2-0-0-0-61 (Audio reel OBJ-1065)
    Professor Rieckhoff interviewed by Dennis Roberts
    Rieckhoff, Klaus E.; Roberts, Dennis; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: R-160-2-0-133.1 orig., F-160-item133.